(Stuart:)Sheldon hired me to go
shopping with you.
(Amy:)Hold on.
(Amy:)He paid you to get out
of spending time with me?
(Stuart:)No, it's not like that.
(Stuart:)There's a long line
he'd rather stand in.
(Stuart:)So what are we doing?
Old Navy, Build-A-Bear?
(Stuart:)I get paid either way.
(Amy:)We're not going
shopping together.
(Stuart:)You sure?
I'm happy to hold your bag.
(Stuart:)And Sheldon gave me money
for a hotdog on a stick.
(Amy:)Can you understand why
I might be annoyed right now?
(chuckles) Look, lady,
I just work here.
(Howard:)We've waited in a lot of
lines together, haven't we?
(Sheldon:)Remember when we camped out
for the Doctor Who panel
at Comic-Con?
(Raj:)Yeah, sleeping under the
stars with other fans
(Raj:)who love the show
as much as we do.
(Leonard:)Waking up, wondering which one
of those fans stole our wallets.
SHELDON: Stuart,
what are you doing here?
(Stuart:)Sheldon, you are the most
inconsiderate person
(Stuart:)I have ever met
in my entire life!